Lucas Baldasso

Fullstack Developer



Contact
Phone:
+55 42 99802-9837
E-mail:
biolucasb@gmail.com

Skills

C# SQL .Net Unity

VSIX and Extension Tools ReactJS WebAPIs

DDD Software Architecture Rust Docker

Profile

Fullstack Developer with a focus on backend development. Has been working as a system developer for three years, having developed several projects throughout his career, from the conception and requirements gathering phase to the maintenance and evolution phase. With project management skills, he plays a significant and recurring role in meetings with clients and in the creation and assignment of tasks based on those meetings and requirement validations. A Software Engineer graduate from Centro Universitário Campo Real in December 2024, he participated in the academic monitoring program throughout the entire course. He conducted scientific research in Object-Oriented Programming, the Pub-Sub development pattern, and Databases, with his final project being a CLI that converts JSON structures into SQL. He also developed a pharmacy management system as an extension activity during the course. Highly capable of teamwork, empathetic, and skilled at sharing knowledge.

Portfolio

https://lbaldasso.dev.br/ https://github.com/lbaldasso/

References

Aidy Health

Experiences

Coding Solutions

Fullstack developer

11/2023 - Current

- · Meetings with clients and requirements gathering
- · Assigned to two distinct projects, one as the lead developer, the other as the team leader
- · Backend development using C#, .NET Core, and SQL Server
- Frontend development using ReactJS, ReduxJS, and Typescript
- · Integration with external APIs for document validation, signatures, notifications, and more
- Development of templates and creation of complex documents
- Development of multi-tenant systems with custom permissions
- Customization of internal forms for client use
- Development and maintenance of migrations
- DevOps and Pipeline Management

Sixtech Systems

Desenvolvedor Fullstack

04/2024 - Atual

- Backend development using C#, .NET Core, and PostgreSQL.
- · Frontend development using Angular and TypeScript.
- Requirement gathering meetings with the client.
- Development of an entity change log system.
- Editing and printing documents based on templates.
- Development and maintenance of migrations.

Aidy Health

Principal Software Engineer

03/2023 - 02/2024

- Coordinate activities in the backend and frontend development team, including task assignment, code review, and code quality assurance.
- Design scalable software architecture and select appropriate microservices for deployment.
- Design and implement RESTful APIs using C# and .NET Core.
- Manage the Azure environment, including the creation of resources, deployment of applications, and monitoring of services.
- Work with Azure Cognitive Services, SignalR, WebSockets, and WebHooks.
- Use Linear as project management tool and GitHub as version control system.

PayeWaive

Fullstack Developer

05/2023 - 09/2023

- Developed automated tests using C# and NUnit.
- Developed new features using C#, .NET Core
- Helped to improve the solution's architecture.
- Worked with Azure DevOps to manage the project.
- · Used Git as version control system.
- Handled File manipulation using C# and .NET Core.

Education

Centro Universitário Campo Real

2021 - 2024

- I am in my sixth semester as an academic monitor for courses such as Computer Systems Programming I and II, Digital Games I and II, and Web/Mobile Development II and III.
- Conducted a research project on Object-Oriented Programming, which was presented at SAPIEN, an Academic Scientific Initiation Week. The project was titled "TEACHING TECHNIQUES AND TOOLS FOR OBJECT-ORIENTED PROGRAMMING".
- I studied and developed an event triggering tool through reflection, which was presented at Sapien in the Innovation category,

Você pode encontrar o código fonte deste currículo aqui Você pode encontrar o mais informações detalhadas das experiências aqui